Guide to the Here is New York Collection 1996-2007 (bulk 2001-2002) PR 258
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: here is new york Images
  - Subseries III: Unreturned Photographs
    - Separated Zip/Floppy Disks, [2001-2002] (Box ZIP1)
      Access to files on zip disks and floppy disks in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series I/Subseries 3
- Series II: Voices of 9.11
  In April of 2002, here is new york launched its oral history initiative, Voices of 9.11. Begun initially as a way for here is new york photographers to tell stories of their images, the project quickly expanded to include 9/11 survivors, family members, first responders, medical workers, area residents and workers, and others. A makeshift video booth was erected at here is new york's 1105 Sixth Avenue exhibition. The speaker controlled the recording; there were no time limits or restrictions on subject matter. When the Sixth Avenue location closed in June, the video booth was relocated to the Prince Street gallery. Later locations included Washington, D.C. (at the Corcoran Gallery exhibit), Shanksville, PA (the crash site of United flight 93), Staten Island, and the Pentagon in January 2003. Some of the testimonies were exhibited in the Prince Street gallery, the Corcoran, and the Pentagon.
  There are 580 testimonies (some speakers recorded twice), which are not numbered consecutively. Videos are arranged by location of recording, then listed by file number and name of speaker. Files are in Quicktime format and vary in length. See the database on HINY computer terminal (and in finding aid binder) for a complete list of Voices of 9.11 participants, as well as information on recording location and participants' contributions to here is new york and roles in 9/11 (if any). The database was created by N-YHS using primarily information from a here is new york database.
  Electronic records for Voices of 9.11 include stills of participants in video booths and office files. Added material includes technical and other information provided by Ruth Sergel, who administered the Voices program for here is new york.
  See Series IV. Subseries I for video documentation of the Voices of 9.11 booth and Pentagon project.
  Access to Voices of 9.11 testimonies is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series II. Voices of 9.11/Voices Testimonies
  - Voices of 9.11 Testimonies (hard drives), 2002-2003 (Box HD1-14)
    Hard drive housing in HD15
  - Added material--Voices program info from Ruth Sergel (documents added to collection in 2007) [Files also on HINY Computer Terminal], [2002] (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Video Booth Stills, 2002 (Box Electronic Records)
    [FILE ACCESS ON HINY COMPUTER TERMINAL]
  - Voices of 9.11 Office Files, 2002-2003 (Box Electronic Records)
  - Hard Drive Housing, Undated (Box HD15)
  - Voices files--Mini-DV back-ups (except Pentagon), Undated (Box MINIDV1-3)
- Series III: Other Donated Material
  This series contains original material donated to here is new york, but not necessarily intended for or used in its photography project or exhibitions. It includes home videos, artwork, music, posters, and non-here is new york exhibit material and images.
  - Subseries I: Home Videos
    Here is new york did not have a formal home video program, but a number of videographers submitted their works in a variety of formats (VHS, CD/DVD, Mini-DV, Beta). Most depict the events of 9/11 in New York City or the aftermath. Some are montages of images, or tributes to the World Trade Center, set to music. There are 39 individual movies in this subseries. In addition, here is new york electronic records contain edited versions of some of these videos, presumably made for gallery display.
    Access to files on CDs and VHS tapes in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series III/Subseries 1
    - Home Video & Displays, 2002-2003 (Box Electronic Records)
      Access to files is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series III/Subseries 1
    - VHS/Beta/Mini-DVs, [2001-2002] (Box VHS1-4, MINIDV3)
      Access to files on VHS and other tapes in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series III/Subseries 1
    - CDs/DVDs, 2001 (Box CD1)
      Access to files on CDs and DVDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series III/Subseries 1
    - Home Video: Separated Housing, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Subseries II: Photographs/Images
    The bulk of this subseries is hundreds of digital images of the Pentagon submitted on CDs by Michael Garcia, a member of the Pentagon's Defense Protective Service. These images are part of the September 11 Bearing Witness to History Collection at the Smithsonian Institution, National Museum of American History. Also included in this subseries is material relating to the architectural exhibition "A New World Trade Center" in 2002, and posters relating to 9/11 or the World Trade Center.
    Access to files on CDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series III/Subseries 2
    - Max Protetech Gallery: A New World Trade Center, [2002] (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Michael Garcia, Pentagon Images: Separated Housing, [2002] (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Oversize: photo montages, 2001, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Oversize: posters, Undated (Box FLAT FILE2-3)
    - Rolled images, Undated (Box PHOTO1)
    - CDs/DVDs, 2001-2002 (Box CD1)
  - Subseries III: Music
    This subseries contains six music CDs, some of which are mixes of previously released songs, and some of which contain original music created about September 11.
    Access to files on CDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series III/Subseries 3
    - Music CDs: Separated Housing, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Music CDs, [2001-2002] (Box CD1)
- Series IV: Documentation of Exhibitions
  - Subseries I: Photographs and Videos of Exhibitions
    This subseries includes photographs and videos of here is new york exhibitions, mostly at the original Prince Street location and the 2002 Chicago show. Chicago photo albums also include staff outings. Images were taken by here is new york staff and outside photographers. Photos of European exhibits can also be found in Series V, Subseries 1: Mark Lubell Office Files (London folder).
    Also included in this subseries are videos of here is new york's 1105 Sixth Avenue location, the Corcoran exhibition, the projection of images on the Astrovision in Times Square, and the Voices of 9.11 project at the Pentagon (see "hiny Documentation"). For specific information on how here is new york mounted exhibitions, see "Hanging Instructions" movie in the Production Department's electronic files (Series V).
    Access to files on CDs and electronic records in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series IV/Subseries 1
    - Prince Street (by Chris Cawley), 2001 (Box 47, Folder 6-8)
    - Prince Street: Clinton visit (Chris Cawley), 2001 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Prince Street (Marcee Raffel), [2002] (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Chicago: Photo album #1 (Maggie Berkvist), 2002 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Chicago: Photo album #2 (Maggie Berkvist), 2002 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Chicago, 2002, [2002] (Box 47, Folder 13-15)
    - Oversize: Prince Street/ICP (includes Clinton visit) [separated from "Brenda Manes: Chicago Snaps"], 2001, undated (Box 72, Folder 2-3)
    - Oversize: Chicago ["Brenda Manes: Chicago Snaps"], [2002] (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Oversize: Other exhibits [separated from "Brenda Manes: Chicago Snaps"], Undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - CDs, 2001-2002 (Box CD1)
      Access to files on CDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series IV/Subseries 1
    - hiny Documentation, [2002-2003] (Box Electronic Records)
    - HINY DOCUMENTATION, [2002-2003] (Box Mini-DV3)
  - Subseries II: Supporting Material/Exhibit Ephemera
    The bulk of this subseries is exhibit signage from various here is new york shows. Also included are slideshows and montages of material on CDs that were presumably screened at exhibitions or outdoor projections.
    Access to files on CDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series IV/Subseries 2
    - Exhibit Handouts: Tokyo, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - HINY Slideshows: Separated housing, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Oversize: Exhibit signage [Prince Street], Undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Oversize: Exhibit signage, Corcoran, Undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Oversize: Exhibit signage, Germany, Undated (Box ART3)
    - Oversize: Exhibit signage, Japan; E.B. White quote, Undated (Box FLAT FILE1,3)
    - CDs, 2001-2002 (Box CD2)
    - Banners: Chicago, [2002] (Box ROLLED)
- Series V: Office Files
  This series contains the supporting files of here is new york that document the internal workings of the organization. The files are arranged into subseries primarily reflecting key here is new york individuals and departments, especially public relations and print production. Also included are here is new york correspondence, staff photographs, and ephemera.
  Voices of 9.11 contains oral history testimonies of several here is new york staff members, including founders Michael Shulan and Charles Traub. See Series II.
  There are no office files for here is new york founders.
  Photographer and other releases are restricted to N-YHS staff use only.
  - Subseries I: Mark Lubell Files
    Mark Lubell was hired in 2002 as a business manager. The bulk of Lubell's files deal with here is new york exhibitions, including planning, agreements, contracts, finances, and travel plans. Other files concern here is new york finances, development, and dissolution. Lubell's CDs and DVDs include promotional material, music, and images from the collection. His VHS cassettes contain video documentation of here is new york exhibits and events (including Bill Clinton's visit to the Prince Street gallery), promotional material and documentaries about here is new york, and other videos related to 9/11.
    Access to files on CDs and VHS tapes in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 1
    - Exhibition Files: Arles/Paris, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Files: Boca Raton, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Files: Chicago, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
    - Exhibition Files: Dublin, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Files: Germany, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Files: Houston--Fotofest, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Files: Japan, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 8-10)
    - Exhibition Files: London--The Guardian [Includes photos of other European exhibits], 2002 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition Files: Louisville--Louisville Free Public Library, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Files: Minneapolis, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition Files: New Jersey--Richard Stockton College, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Files: Ohio--Marietta College, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition Files: Russia, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Exhibition Files: San Diego, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Exhibition Files: Tampa, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Exhibition Files: Troy, N.Y., 2002 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition Files: Washington, D.C., 2002 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Files: Zurich, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Files: Madame Tussaud's, New York, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Files: General, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 4-5)
    - Exhibition Files: Sample contract, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Prince Street: Equipment loan, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Prince Street: Image list, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Telerama--Paris, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - HINY Dissolution--Strategic planning, 2002, [2002] (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - HINY Dissolution--Appraisal/Donations, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition Reimbursed Expenses, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Financial Documents, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Financial Statements, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Tax Documents, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Fundraising/Development, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Ground Zero Memorial, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Notes/Postcards, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Personnel/Contacts, 2002, undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Brendan Gill Prize, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - HINY Promotional Material, [2002] (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Promotional Material--Other, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - CDs, 2001-2002 (Box CD2)
      Access to files on CDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 1
    - VHS tapes, 2002, undated (Box VHS5)
      Access to files on VHS tapes in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 1
  - Subseries II: Public Relations
    This subseries contains material related to here is new york publicity and media relations, including press kits, clippings, and periodicals. Also included are office files of two PR staff members, as well as material pertaining to the publication of here is new york's book in 2002. CDs and DVDs contain here is new york images, footage of here is new york television press coverage, press kit and publicity material, and photos of here is new york exhibits and events. VHS tapes contain press coverage of here is new york in the U.S., Europe, and Japan.
    Access to files on CDs and VHS tapes in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 2
    - Photo Requests, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 1-7)
    - SCALO--Serialization Rights, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - SCALO--Serialization Rights, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - Indemnification Forms--Media, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
    - Chicago Exhibit--Preview briefing book, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Exhibit--Media coverage, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Amy Wentz files, 2002, undated (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
    - Stephanie Schenppe files, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
    - Bid, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Publicity Photos: Book, [2002] (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Press Kit Components and Press Releases, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Press Kit Components, 2001-2002, undated (Box 52, Folder 7-9)
    - Press Kit Components, 2001-2002, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Press Kits, 2002, [2002] (Box 53, Folder 2-3)
    - Press Kits--Chicago, 2002, [2002] (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Press Kits--Corcoran, 2002, [2002] (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
    - Press Kits--Various contents/Incomplete, 2002, [2002] (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Press Kits--Various contents/Incomplete, 2002, [2002] (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
    - Press Clippings--Binder, 2001-2002 (Box 54, Folder 4-7)
    - Press Clippings/Releases, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
    - Magazines--Domestic, 2001-2002 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Magazines--Domestic, 2001-2002 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
    - Magazines--Foreign--British, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Magazines--Foreign--French, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Magazines--Foreign--German, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 5-6)
    - Magazines--Foreign--Japanese, 2001, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Magazines--Foreign--Dutch, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - 9-11 Meditations at the Center of the World, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Exhibit/Award Brochures and Newsletters, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Exhibit Promotional Cards, [2001, 2002] (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - September 11th Fund Brochures, [2002] (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Children's Aid Society Annual Report, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Oversize: Periodicals, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Brochures--ICP, [2002] (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Oversize: Clippings, [2001] (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Oversize: Duplicates, [2001] (Box 72, Folder 11-13)
    - Oversize: Newspapers, complete, 2002 (Box OV-NEWS)
    - CDs, 2001-2002 (Box CD2)
      Access to files on CDs tapes in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 2
    - VHS tapes, 2001-2002, undated (Box VHS5-7)
      Access to files on VHS tapes in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 2
  - Subseries III: Production Department
    The Production Department (also known as the Print Department) created prints for sale and exhibition. Much of this department's files relates to specific exhibits and includes image lists and contact sheets. Other office files in this subseries pertain to special orders, specific databases, and equipment. CDs contain mostly images for exhibits, print databases, and instructions for hanging here is new york shows. Production Department artifacts include a pair of handling gloves and 3-D glasses.
    Access to files on CDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 3
    - Production Folder, 2001-2002 (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
    - Print Production Early Files [Lara McPherson files], 2001-2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Files: Berlin, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Files: Boca Raton, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition Files: Chicago, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition Files: Corcoran, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition Files: Daytona, [2002] (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition Files: Las Vegas, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition Files: Minnesota, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition Files: Ohio, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition Files: San Diego, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition Files: Tampa, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Files:[Troy, N.Y.], Fulton St., 2002 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Files: Traveling Exhibit Print List, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Files: Traveling Show Documents, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - HBO, Undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Lake Geneve Order, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Special Order Requests, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Book, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - HINY Prospectus, 2002, [2002] (Box 57, Folder 9-10)
    - Print Dept. Inventory, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Scanning and Retouch Lists, Undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Missing Images Database, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Internet Comments, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence/Photo Requests, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Jacob Peck Digital Fulfillment, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Media Kits, [2002] (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Print Dept. and Office Wall Art, 2002, undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Calendars, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Epson Invoices, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Fed Ex Deliveries, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Uline Supply Catalog, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Catalogs/Contact Sheets--500 Print Show, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Catalogs/Contact Sheets--Chicago, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Catalogs/Contact Sheets--Las Vegas [full size prints], Undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Catalogs/Contact Sheets--Arles, [2002] (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Catalogs/Contact Sheets--Berlin, Boca Raton, Ohio, Tampa, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Catalogs/Contact Sheets--Firefighters, Flight 93, Pentagon, Scalo, Elton John, 2002, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Oversize: Exhibit Catalogs/Contact Sheets--Other/Unknown, 2002, undated (Box 73, Folder 7-9)
    - Oversize: Original Prints, 2001, undated (Box 73, Folder 10-11)
    - Oversize: HINY Prospectus, [2002] (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Oversize: Print Dept. and Office Wall Art, Undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box FLAT FILE1)
    - CDs, 2001-2002 (Box CD3)
      Access to files on CDs in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 3 (EXCEPT- HINY images for 500 Print Show- 17 CDs)
    - Artifacts: White gloves, 3-D glasses, Undated (Box ART2)
    - 6 copies of DVD WTC: The First Twenty-Four Hours (see Series VI), 2001 (Box WTC1)
  - Subseries IV: Digital Archives Department
    Bulk are image databases and inventories.
    - Image Databases/Inventories; Office Files, 2001-2002 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - Subseries V: Intake Department
    The intake department accepted and processed donated images.
    Access to files on the CD in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 5
    - Submission Guidelines, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 1 CD - images [separated from releases], 2002 (Box CD3)
  - Subseries VI: Correspondence
    Correspondence from here is new york concerns funding, former President Bill Clinton's visit, and the here is new york book. The letters and emails in this subseries are primarily from photographers, exhibit-goers, and well-wishers.
    - HINY to others, 2001-2002 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - To HINY, 2001-2002 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Re: Book, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - General, 2001-2002 (Box 58, Folder 8-9)
    - Memo, Undated [2002] (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Subseries VII: Staff Photographs
    This subseries contains mainly images of here is new york staff members and volunteers. The bulk is printed photographs, but there are also several digital images. Also included are group photos of ~ 400 here is new york photographers, taken April 2002 at a party for the photographers at the 1105 Sixth Avenue location. The CD in this subseries has images of photographer Chris Callis taking this group photographer photo. Here is new york staff members and volunteers can also be seen in some photographs of exhibits in Series IV (especially Chicago photo albums).
    For videos of HINY staff and volunteers see "hiny Documentation" electronic file in Series IV. Subseries I. Some workers also participated in the Voices of 9.11 project (Series II); the Voices database identifies HINY staff and volunteers.
    Access to files on CD in this subseries is on HINY computer terminal at: HINY Collection Series I, III-V/Series V/Subseries 7
    - Group Photos, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 11-12)
    - Staff Events/At Work, 2001-2002, undated (Box 58, Folder 13-17)
    - Infinity Awards, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Group Photo: Photographers, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Ground Zero and area [taken by staff?], 2001, undated (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - CD, 2002 (Box CD3)
    - hiny group photo & text 4.1.02, 2002 (Box Electronic Records)
    - HINY staff, 2001-2002 (Box Electronic Records)
  - Subseries VIII: Ephemera/Artifacts
    This subseries contains brochures of ceremonies for two awards won by here is new york (Brendan Gill Award and Cornell Capa Award) in 2002. Also included are office ephemera and artifacts including a patriotic mirror, flags, an album recording of E.B. White's "Here is New York," and VHS tapes unrelated to 9/11.
    - Award Brochures, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Office Ephemera, 2001-2002, undated (Box 59, Folder 6-9)
    - Artifacts, Undated (Box ART2-3)
    - Videos: A Cry from the Grave; Tony Bennett special, 1996, undated (Box VHS7)
  - Subseries IX: Releases
    Includes original releases for images, Voices of 9.11, home videos, and the here is new york book. Arranged by project, then alphabetically. There are unfiled releases in the beginning of some sections. Voices of 9.11 releases are labeled Video Booth.
    RELEASES RESTRICTED TO N-YHS STAFF USE ONLY
    - Releases, 2001-2003 (Box 59-68)
- Series VI: WTC: The First Twenty-Four Hours